<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Policy &amp; Security Think Tank Updates</title><link>https://github.com/YOUR_USERNAME/YOUR_REPO</link><description>Custom RSS feed from CSIS, CFR, and other policy institutions</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:13:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Sudan’s Humanitarian Emergency</title><link>https://www.cfr.org/event/sudans-humanitarian-emergency</link><description>Panelists discuss the status of the conflict in Sudan, including the deteriorating condition of civilians, the prospect for regional stability, and the options for an international response.This is a virtual meeting through Zoom.Log-in information and instructions on how to participate during the question-and-answer portion will be provided the evening before the event to those who register.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cfr.org/event/sudans-humanitarian-emergency</guid></item><item><title>The Pentagon’s AI Problem Isn’t Algorithms, It’s Evaluation</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/pentagons-ai-problem-isnt-algorithms-its-evaluation</link><description>Current AI benchmarks were not designed for the realities of war. Without defense-specific evaluation, AI systems risk being deployed without evidence they improve military judgment or outcomes.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/analysis/pentagons-ai-problem-isnt-algorithms-its-evaluation</guid></item><item><title>Ryan Berg in Foreign Policy: Trump’s Western Hemisphere Pivot Is Real</title><link>https://foreignpolicy.com/2025/12/19/trump-western-hemisphere-pivot-nss</link><description>Americas Program Director Ryan C. Berg contends that if President Trump wants to make good on the new National Security Strategy, the United States must recalibrate its defense posture.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://foreignpolicy.com/2025/12/19/trump-western-hemisphere-pivot-nss</guid></item><item><title>Improving Transparency and Human Rights in Procurement: An Incentive-Based Approach</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/improving-transparency-and-human-rights-procurement-incentive-based-approach</link><description>The substantial U.S. purchasing power creates significant opportunities to foster positive change in supply chains and makes government procurement an important, and underutilized, inroad for the protection of human rights.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/analysis/improving-transparency-and-human-rights-procurement-incentive-based-approach</guid></item></channel></rss>