<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Policy &amp; Security Think Tank Updates</title><link>https://github.com/YOUR_USERNAME/YOUR_REPO</link><description>Custom RSS feed from CSIS, CFR, and other policy institutions</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:58:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Tech Edge: A Living Playbook for America’s Technology Long Game</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/tech-edge-living-playbook-americas-technology-long-game</link><description>Winning the tech race is not about any single breakthrough. Leadership requires competing across the full menu of technologies, developing the dexterity to build at speed and scale, and defending our domestic markets from nonmarket competition.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/analysis/tech-edge-living-playbook-americas-technology-long-game</guid></item><item><title>The Future of the WHO—and How the United States Can Shape It</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/future-who-and-how-united-states-can-shape-it</link><description>The United States will officially end its relationship with the World Health Organization on January 22, 2026. But this break potentially opens the way for the next phase of reform. A smart transition back into U.S. membership is a path that will advance U.S. interests.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/analysis/future-who-and-how-united-states-can-shape-it</guid></item><item><title>Bright Shiny Objects</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/bright-shiny-objects</link><description>This week, Bill Reinsch argues that the Trump administration’s approach to policymaking weakens public understanding and accountability.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/analysis/bright-shiny-objects</guid></item><item><title>The Geopolitics of Maduro’s Capture: What Does Operation Absolute Resolve Mean for Russia?</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/geopolitics-maduros-capture-what-does-operation-absolute-resolve-mean-russia</link><description>CSIS Americas Program Associate Fellow Henry Ziemer assesses the implications of the recent U.S. capture of Nicolás Maduro for Russia's strategy in the Western Hemisphere.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/analysis/geopolitics-maduros-capture-what-does-operation-absolute-resolve-mean-russia</guid></item><item><title>AI and Global Food Security: A Focus on Early Warning Systems</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/ai-and-global-food-security-focus-early-warning-systems</link><description>AI promises to improve food security early warning systems, which help inform decisionmakers and prevent hunger before it arises. CSIS experts unpack the risks and benefits of AI-enabled tools for food security early warning systems around the world.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/analysis/ai-and-global-food-security-focus-early-warning-systems</guid></item></channel></rss>