<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Policy &amp; Security Think Tank Updates</title><link>https://github.com/YOUR_USERNAME/YOUR_REPO</link><description>Custom RSS feed from CSIS, CFR, and other policy institutions</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 01:16:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Satellite Imagery Analysis of China’s Alleged 2020 Nuclear Test at Lop Nur</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/satellite-imagery-analysis-chinas-alleged-2020-nuclear-test-lop-nur</link><description>New claims of supercritical testing at Lop Nur suggest China is improving the science that supports its nuclear arsenal. The United States should proceed carefully to avoid a renewed era of unrestrained nuclear testing.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/analysis/satellite-imagery-analysis-chinas-alleged-2020-nuclear-test-lop-nur</guid></item><item><title>Critical Minerals Ministerial Introduces New International Cooperation Strategy</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/critical-minerals-ministerial-introduces-new-international-cooperation-strategy</link><description>At the inaugural Critical Minerals Ministerial, 55 foreign ministers convened to advance minerals security through new bilateral and plurilateral frameworks, marking a shift toward coordinated, market-shaping efforts to stabilize prices and strengthen allied supply chains.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/analysis/critical-minerals-ministerial-introduces-new-international-cooperation-strategy</guid></item><item><title>The Rise of “Watt’s Law” and Why Power Could Put a Ceiling on American Innovation</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/rise-watts-law-and-why-power-could-put-ceiling-american-innovation</link><description>A foundational advantage of the U.S. digital economy is weakening. For decades, Moore’s Law and Dennard scaling delivered steady improvements in computing performance while keeping energy costs manageable and underpinning productivity growth and national security.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/analysis/rise-watts-law-and-why-power-could-put-ceiling-american-innovation</guid></item></channel></rss>