<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Policy &amp; Security Think Tank Updates</title><link>https://github.com/YOUR_USERNAME/YOUR_REPO</link><description>Custom RSS feed from CSIS, CFR, and other policy institutions</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 00:22:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Industrial Policy Is Back—And Minerals Are at the Center</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/industrial-policy-back-and-minerals-are-center</link><description>The United States has revived its industrial policy playbook to support critical minerals through price floors, stockpiles, and equity. But in a sector shaped by geology, cost curves, and market risk, durable security depends on commercial viability—not just public capital.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/analysis/industrial-policy-back-and-minerals-are-center</guid></item><item><title>How Would Iran Respond to a U.S. Attack?</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/how-would-iran-respond-us-attack</link><description>If the United States strikes Iran, how will Tehran respond? History suggests a calibrated mix of cyberattacks, drones, maritime pressure, and limited missile strikes designed to signal resolve while avoiding a wider regional war.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/analysis/how-would-iran-respond-us-attack</guid></item><item><title>Criminal Kingpin “El Mencho” Is Dead, What Comes Next?</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/criminal-kingpin-el-mencho-dead-what-comes-next</link><description>CSIS Americas Program Director Ryan C. Berg and Henry Ziemer analyze the implications of criminal kingpin El Mencho's death at the hands of Mexican security forces.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/analysis/criminal-kingpin-el-mencho-dead-what-comes-next</guid></item><item><title>The United States–Republic of Korea Alliance: Strengthening Extended Nuclear Deterrence in a Shifting Strategic Landscape</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/united-states-republic-korea-alliance-strengthening-extended-nuclear-deterrence-shifting</link><description>As new and enduring uncertainties shape the Indo-Pacific and the U.S.-ROK alliance, the Asan Institute and CSIS conducted a joint project to assess extended nuclear deterrence cooperation within the alliance and recommend ways to strengthen its credibility and resilience.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/analysis/united-states-republic-korea-alliance-strengthening-extended-nuclear-deterrence-shifting</guid></item></channel></rss>