<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Policy &amp; Security Think Tank Updates</title><link>https://github.com/YOUR_USERNAME/YOUR_REPO</link><description>Custom RSS feed from CSIS, CFR, and other policy institutions</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 06:05:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>‘America First’ Meets the National Security and Defense Strategies</title><link>/expert-brief/america-first-meets-national-security-and-defense-strategies</link><description>Will the two congressionally mandated documents provide some clarity about President Trump’s priorities and strategy?</description><guid isPermaLink="false">/expert-brief/america-first-meets-national-security-and-defense-strategies</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 06:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump’s Focus on Christians Misses Boko Haram’s Wider Threat in Nigeria</title><link>/expert-brief/trumps-focus-christians-misses-boko-harams-wider-threat-nigeria</link><description>The Trump administration’s accusations that Nigeria is allowing targeted killings of Christians distract from the bigger problem of jihadist and other forms of indiscriminate violence.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">/expert-brief/trumps-focus-christians-misses-boko-harams-wider-threat-nigeria</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 06:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Overcoming a Culture of Secrecy: Can the United States Kick its National Security Over-Classification Habit?</title><link>/event/overcoming-culture-secrecy-can-united-states-kick-its-national-security-over-classification</link><description>The United States faces evolving threats from China, Russia, Iran, and North Korea, but a culture of overclassification of intelligence results in the routine failure to share vital information at speed and scale. In an example of bipartisanship, panelists discuss how the United States can reform its national security information policies, regulations, and laws to ensure crucial insights are shared quickly and effectively across government.&#13;
&#13;
Please note there is no Zoom component to the meeting.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">/event/overcoming-culture-secrecy-can-united-states-kick-its-national-security-over-classification</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 06:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Putin’s Nuclear Offer: How to Navigate a New START Extension</title><link>/expert-brief/putins-nuclear-offer-how-navigate-new-start-extension</link><description>The United States should not fall for Putin’s gambit to undercut Ukraine. Before agreeing to an extension, it must secure greater verification guarantees and a commitment to further negotiations.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">/expert-brief/putins-nuclear-offer-how-navigate-new-start-extension</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 06:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Conflict in Cambodia and Thailand Resumes—With No End in Sight</title><link>/article/conflict-cambodia-and-thailand-resumes-no-end-sight</link><description>Weeks after a Trump-negotiated ceasefire fell apart, the two countries seem far from finding another pause in the fighting. In fact, the border conflict is likely to get worse.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">/article/conflict-cambodia-and-thailand-resumes-no-end-sight</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 06:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>DoD's AI Balancing Act</title><link>/article/dods-ai-balancing-act</link><description>To secure a strategic advantage, the DoD must manage the tension between vendor hype and extreme alarmism regarding AI adoption.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">/article/dods-ai-balancing-act</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 06:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Mapping the U.S. Military Buildup Near Venezuela</title><link>/article/mapping-us-military-buildup-near-venezuela</link><description>The United States has significantly increased its military presence near Venezuela, carrying out strikes on alleged drug boats in the Caribbean Sea and threatening Nicolás Maduro’s regime with the possibility of invasion.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">/article/mapping-us-military-buildup-near-venezuela</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 06:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Can the New Gang Suppression Force Bring Relief to Haiti?</title><link>/article/can-new-gang-suppression-force-bring-relief-haiti</link><description>The UN authorization of a new security mission in Haiti marks an escalation in efforts to curb surging gang violence. Aimed at alleviating a worsening humanitarian crisis, its militarized approach has nevertheless raised concerns about repeating mistakes from previous interventions.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">/article/can-new-gang-suppression-force-bring-relief-haiti</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 06:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ceremonial Foreign Policy</title><link>/blog/ceremonial-foreign-policy</link><description>In shallowly engaging with Kinshasa and Kigali, Washington does little to promote peace and risks insulating leaders from accountability.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">/blog/ceremonial-foreign-policy</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 06:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Can Break Maduro’s Hold of Venezuela Without a War</title><link>/expert-brief/trump-can-break-maduros-hold-venezuela-without-war</link><description>The opposition and the Maduro regime will face a new variable at the negotiating table: the United States and its heavy military presence off Venezuela’s coast. As a direct party, the Trump administration now has an opportunity to learn the lessons of the past to bring a potential conflict to a close.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">/expert-brief/trump-can-break-maduros-hold-venezuela-without-war</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 06:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Postcard from Cotonou</title><link>/blog/postcard-cotonou</link><description>Foiled or not, the attempted military takeover in Benin bodes ill for political stability in West Africa.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">/blog/postcard-cotonou</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 06:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Thailand and Cambodia Head Back to Battle, Presaging Possible War</title><link>/blog/thailand-and-cambodia-head-back-battle-presaging-possible-war</link><description>Weeks after a Trump-negotiated ceasefire fell apart and Thailand hit Cambodia with air strikes, the two countries seem far from finding another pause, and it is unlikely the U.S. president will step back in.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">/blog/thailand-and-cambodia-head-back-battle-presaging-possible-war</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 06:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Are We Ready? | Trump’s National Security Strategy, With Rebecca Lissner</title><link>/podcasts/tpi/are-we-ready-trumps-national-security-strategy-rebecca-lissner</link><description>Rebecca Lissner, senior fellow for U.S. foreign policy at the Council, sits down with James M. Lindsay to discuss the Trump administration's new National Security Strategy and its consequences for U.S. foreign and defense policy.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">/podcasts/tpi/are-we-ready-trumps-national-security-strategy-rebecca-lissner</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 06:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>In Myanmar, the World’s Indifference to Authoritarianism Is on Full Display</title><link>/blog/myanmar-worlds-indifference-authoritarianism-full-display</link><description>Myanmar’s upcoming, tightly controlled “elections” are designed to manufacture legitimacy for the junta, which hopes the mere act of holding a vote will ease its international isolation despite the ongoing civil war.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">/blog/myanmar-worlds-indifference-authoritarianism-full-display</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 06:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Forecasting Humanitarian Risk in 2026: A Conversation With David Miliband</title><link>/event/forecasting-humanitarian-risk-2026-conversation-david-miliband</link><description>David Miliband, president and chief executive officer of the International Rescue Committee (IRC), presents the new IRC Emergency Watchlist report, highlighting the countries at highest risk of humanitarian crises in 2026 and examining where the international community has made progress or fallen short.&#13;
&#13;
For those attending virtually, log-in information and instructions on how to participate during the question-and-answer portion will be provided the evening before the event to those who register.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">/event/forecasting-humanitarian-risk-2026-conversation-david-miliband</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 06:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Stabilizing Cobalt Markets: A Price Floor for U.S. Minerals Security</title><link>/analysis/stabilizing-cobalt-markets-price-floor-us-minerals-security</link><description>U.S. cobalt security is threatened by severe price volatility driven by PRC oversupply, which has pushed Western mines—including the only U.S. cobalt mine—offline. The United States should use a price floor for strategic projects needed for national and economic security.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">/analysis/stabilizing-cobalt-markets-price-floor-us-minerals-security</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 06:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Experts React: The NSS and Washington’s New Approach to the Western Hemisphere</title><link>/analysis/experts-react-nss-and-washingtons-new-approach-western-hemisphere</link><description>CSIS Americas experts weigh in on the implications of the U.S. National Security Strategy for the Western Hemisphere.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">/analysis/experts-react-nss-and-washingtons-new-approach-western-hemisphere</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 06:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Navigating the Divide: Why the U.S. Navy Must Resume FONOPs in Indonesia</title><link>/analysis/navigating-divide-why-us-navy-must-resume-fonops-indonesia</link><description>For nearly a decade, the U.S. has quietly acquiesced to Indonesia’s restrictive maritime claims to avoid diplomatic friction. This policy has failed. To prevent a catastrophic loss of access during a future crisis, the U.S. Navy must resume targeted Freedom of Navigation Operations.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">/analysis/navigating-divide-why-us-navy-must-resume-fonops-indonesia</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 06:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Did the United States Seize a Venezuelan Oil Shipment?</title><link>/analysis/why-did-united-states-seize-venezuelan-oil-shipment</link><description>By itself, the U.S. seizure of a Venezuelan oil cargo won’t rattle oil markets. But it likely signals a new commitment to sanctions enforcement that will complicate “shadow fleet” operations and ratchet up the pressure on Maduro to step aside.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">/analysis/why-did-united-states-seize-venezuelan-oil-shipment</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 06:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Protecting Subsea Cables: Detect to Deter, Sue to Secure</title><link>/analysis/protecting-subsea-cables-detect-deter-sue-secure</link><description>Subsea cables power global commerce. Though rare, cable attacks impose real costs. But leading technologies are democratizing maritime data and deterring would-be saboteurs. To further deter intentional cable attacks, cable owners should aggressively pursue legal remedies.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">/analysis/protecting-subsea-cables-detect-deter-sue-secure</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 06:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Breaking the Debt Trap: Why Spending Smarter Beats Spending More</title><link>/analysis/breaking-debt-trap-why-spending-smarter-beats-spending-more</link><description>In this commentary, Philip Luck and Michael H. Gary argue efficient public spending is the key to unlocking growth in challenging fiscal environments characterized by rising debt and slowing growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">/analysis/breaking-debt-trap-why-spending-smarter-beats-spending-more</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 06:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What Does the Development Finance Corporation Reauthorization Mean for Energy?</title><link>/analysis/what-does-development-finance-corporation-reauthorization-mean-energy</link><description>Congress is set to reauthorize the DFC through 2031, with potentially significant implications for U.S. energy strategy.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">/analysis/what-does-development-finance-corporation-reauthorization-mean-energy</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 06:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Targeting State AI Laws Undermines, Rather than Advances, U.S. Technology Leadership</title><link>/analysis/targeting-state-ai-laws-undermines-rather-advances-us-technology-leadership</link><description>Aalok Mehta examines President Trump’s new executive order targeting state AI laws, arguing that preempting state legislation before a federal framework exists risks public trust, slows AI adoption, and undermines U.S. technology leadership globally.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">/analysis/targeting-state-ai-laws-undermines-rather-advances-us-technology-leadership</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 06:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>