<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Policy &amp; Security Think Tank Updates</title><link>https://github.com/YOUR_USERNAME/YOUR_REPO</link><description>Custom RSS feed from CSIS, CFR, and other policy institutions</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:32:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Kate E. Koren Joins the CSIS Economics Program as Deputy Director</title><link>https://www.csis.org/news/kate-e-koren-joins-csis-economics-program-deputy-director</link><description>The Center for Strategic and International Studies (CSIS) announced today that Kate E. Koren has joined the CSIS Economics Program and Scholl Chair in International Business as deputy director.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/news/kate-e-koren-joins-csis-economics-program-deputy-director</guid></item><item><title>Building a True Trusted Trade Partnership with the United Kingdom</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/building-true-trusted-trade-partnership-united-kingdom</link><description>Meredith Broadbent unpacks the recent agreement between the United States and United Kingdom to cooperate on pharmaceuticals and medical technology.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/analysis/building-true-trusted-trade-partnership-united-kingdom</guid></item><item><title>How Syria Can Succeed in Integrating the Kurds</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/how-syria-can-succeed-integrating-kurds</link><description>Intensified conflict between the Syrian government and the Kurdish-led Syrian Democratic Forces could threaten Syria’s transition. Here’s what the government can do to ensure it doesn’t.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/analysis/how-syria-can-succeed-integrating-kurds</guid></item><item><title>When to Use (and Not Use) “As a Service” for Government Space Requirements</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/when-use-and-not-use-service-government-space-requirements</link><description>Instead of buying a piece of equipment, which the government then owns and operates, the government is increasingly turning to “as-a-service” models for buying things from space. But how should the government decide between a service model or a traditional one?</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/analysis/when-use-and-not-use-service-government-space-requirements</guid></item></channel></rss>