<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Policy &amp; Security Think Tank Updates</title><link>https://github.com/YOUR_USERNAME/YOUR_REPO</link><description>Custom RSS feed from CSIS, CFR, and other policy institutions</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:06:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Conflicts to Watch in 2026</title><link>https://www.cfr.org/report/conflicts-watch-2026</link><description>The world continues to grow more violent and disorderly. According to CFR’s annual conflict risk assessment, American foreign policy experts are acutely concerned about conflict-related threats to U.S. national security and international stability that are likely to emerge or intensify in 2026. In this report, surveyed experts rate global conflicts by their likelihood and potential harm to U.S. interests and, for the first time, identify opportunities for preventive action.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cfr.org/report/conflicts-watch-2026</guid></item><item><title>The Risk Report for 2026</title><link>https://www.cfr.org/podcasts/wim/risk-report-2026</link><description>Every year, CFR’s Preventive Priorities Survey analyzes existing and potential conflicts throughout the world in terms of likelihood and possible impact. As the second Trump administration reorders U.S. foreign policy priorities, important questions remain about the country’s role in mitigating global conflict. Is the U.S. diplomatically prepared for the multitude of evolving conflicts worldwide and for new challenges on the horizon?</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cfr.org/podcasts/wim/risk-report-2026</guid></item><item><title>Five Takeaways From CFR’s 2026 Conflict Risk Assessment</title><link>https://www.cfr.org/article/five-takeaways-cfrs-2026-conflict-risk-assessment</link><description>Every year, the Preventive Priority Survey asks experts to rank thirty conflict scenarios in terms of likelihood and potential impact. This year’s results paint a picture of a more violent and dangerous world in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cfr.org/article/five-takeaways-cfrs-2026-conflict-risk-assessment</guid></item><item><title>Ryan Berg in Americas Quarterly: A Roadmap for Venezuela’s Future Transition</title><link>https://www.americasquarterly.org/article/a-roadmap-for-venezuelas-future-transition</link><description>Americas Program Director Ryan C. Berg argues that following a transition, the United States must continue humanitarian aid, investment, and renewed diplomatic efforts to ensure the delivery of essential services and support a free Venezuela.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.americasquarterly.org/article/a-roadmap-for-venezuelas-future-transition</guid></item></channel></rss>