<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Policy &amp; Security Think Tank Updates</title><link>https://github.com/YOUR_USERNAME/YOUR_REPO</link><description>Custom RSS feed from CSIS, CFR, and other policy institutions</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 19:50:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CSIS Economic Security and Technology Department Names Angela Paolini Ellard as Non-Resident Senior Adviser</title><link>https://www.csis.org/news/csis-economic-security-and-technology-department-names-angela-paolini-ellard-non-resident</link><description>The Center for Strategic and International Studies (CSIS) today announced that Angela Ellard has been appointed as non-resident senior adviser with the CSIS Economic Security and Technology (EST) Department.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/news/csis-economic-security-and-technology-department-names-angela-paolini-ellard-non-resident</guid></item><item><title>Chinese Buoys Near the South Korea-China PMZ</title><link>https://beyondparallel.csis.org/chinese-buoys-near-the-south-korea-china-pmz</link><description>China’s deployment of buoys near the Korea-China PMZ signals expanding monitoring and gray zone pressure in the Yellow Sea (West Sea).</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://beyondparallel.csis.org/chinese-buoys-near-the-south-korea-china-pmz</guid></item><item><title>Universities, Patents, and the Future of U.S. Competitiveness</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/universities-patents-and-future-us-competitiveness</link><description>The strength of the United States’ innovation system does not rest on government spending alone, but on the mutually supportive partnership between public investment, university research, and private enterprise.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/analysis/universities-patents-and-future-us-competitiveness</guid></item><item><title>The United States Needs Its Marine Corps Now More Than Ever</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/united-states-needs-its-marine-corps-now-more-ever</link><description>Recent arguments for abolishing the Marine Corps on the grounds of redundancy and fiscal constraints overlook the service's unique role as a scalable, naval expeditionary force essential for power projection and sea control in the era of great power competition.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/analysis/united-states-needs-its-marine-corps-now-more-ever</guid></item><item><title>Everything Old Is New Again</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/everything-old-new-again</link><description>In this commentary, Bill Reinsch looks back at past trade analysis that got it right and saw today's trade challenges before everyone else saw them coming, with takeaways for today's leaders.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/analysis/everything-old-new-again</guid></item></channel></rss>