<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Policy &amp; Security Think Tank Updates</title><link>https://github.com/YOUR_USERNAME/YOUR_REPO</link><description>Custom RSS feed from CSIS, CFR, and other policy institutions</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:18:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Unstable Coins: Stablecoin Regulation, Market Structure Legislation, and U.S. Security Risks</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/unstable-coins-stablecoin-regulation-market-structure-legislation-and-us-security-risks</link><description>If policymakers do not urgently refine and implement cryptocurrency regulation, existing stablecoin and market-structure frameworks risk embedding systemic financial and national security vulnerabilities.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/analysis/unstable-coins-stablecoin-regulation-market-structure-legislation-and-us-security-risks</guid></item><item><title>Profit from Preparation: Innovations and Opportunities in Disaster Risk Financing in Developing Countries</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/profit-preparation-innovations-and-opportunities-disaster-risk-financing-developing</link><description>A combination of extreme weather impacts and cuts to aid budgets mean that the next few years will be ripe for the rapid development and further scaling up of anticipatory action measures and prearranged finance approaches to better manage mounting disaster risk.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/analysis/profit-preparation-innovations-and-opportunities-disaster-risk-financing-developing</guid></item><item><title>Disaster Risk Financing in Fragile Contexts: Syria Case Study</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/disaster-risk-financing-fragile-contexts-syria-case-study</link><description>Syria experienced a twice a century drought in the first few months of 2025, and it was through innovative disaster risk financing that WFP was able to raise the funds needed to respond.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/analysis/disaster-risk-financing-fragile-contexts-syria-case-study</guid></item><item><title>Disaster Risk Financing in Real Time: Ghana Case Study</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/disaster-risk-financing-real-time-ghana-case-study</link><description>Recognizing the growing impacts of climate change and the increased importance of preparation for extreme weather events, the government of Ghana has undertaken several steps in recent years to enhance resilience by securing prearranged financing for disasters.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/analysis/disaster-risk-financing-real-time-ghana-case-study</guid></item></channel></rss>