<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Policy &amp; Security Think Tank Updates</title><link>https://github.com/YOUR_USERNAME/YOUR_REPO</link><description>Custom RSS feed from CSIS, CFR, and other policy institutions</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:21:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Preventive Priorities Survey Launch: What to Worry About in 2026</title><link>https://www.cfr.org/event/preventive-priorities-survey-launch-what-worry-about-2026</link><description>This event will explore the results of the 2026 Preventive Priorities Survey which polls hundreds of foreign policy experts every year to assess thirty ongoing or potential violent conflicts and their likely impact on U.S. interests.&#13;
&#13;
For those attending virtually, log-in information and instructions on how to participate during the question-and-answer portion will be provided the evening before the event to those who register.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cfr.org/event/preventive-priorities-survey-launch-what-worry-about-2026</guid></item><item><title>The Trump Administration’s Push for Greenland: What to Know</title><link>https://www.cfr.org/article/greenlands-independence-what-would-mean-us-interests</link><description>U.S. President Donald Trump has cast renewed focus on acquiring Greenland. The administration’s increasingly assertive push to take control of the Danish territory could have significant consequences for both the Arctic and the NATO alliance.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cfr.org/article/greenlands-independence-what-would-mean-us-interests</guid></item><item><title>An “America First” Tech Stack Cannot Be America Alone</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/america-first-tech-stack-cannot-be-america-alone</link><description>The administration has not yet revealed the details of the American AI Exports Program and how it will work.  To successfully compete with China, it should include the entire tech stack, facilitate cooperation with trusted partners, and be backed by real resources.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/analysis/america-first-tech-stack-cannot-be-america-alone</guid></item><item><title>A New Rift in the Gulf, and Only the Gulf Can Solve It</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/new-rift-gulf-and-only-gulf-can-solve-it</link><description>Saudi Arabia and the United Arab Emirates have a lot in common. Instead of fostering cooperation, it led to rivalry.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/analysis/new-rift-gulf-and-only-gulf-can-solve-it</guid></item><item><title>Understanding Global South Perspectives on Taiwan</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/understanding-global-south-perspectives-taiwan</link><description>The CSIS Freeman Chair convened an international task force on Taiwan and the Global South. Members evaluated the state of Taiwan’s relationships in the Global South, opportunities to expand engagement, and Global South perspectives on cross-Strait issues.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.csis.org/analysis/understanding-global-south-perspectives-taiwan</guid></item></channel></rss>